## **Liana Rawlings**

0422031678 rawlingsliana@gmail.com

2/11 Palmer street Oakleigh, VIC 3166

#### **Profile**

As a dedicated individual with more than 7 years experience in customer service roles, I have successfully transferred the valuable skills learnt in the hospitality, retail and automotive industries to my work experience in drug policy at Penington Institute. I pride myself in my ability to adapt to evolving situations, learn from my various experiences, and continuously strive for improvement professionally and in my education.

### **Work Experience**

## Digital Communications Coordinator Penington Institute November 2017 - Present

### Social Media Management

Responsibilities include coordinating with the digital communication's team regarding content scheduling for all social media and web channels, as well as campaign direction and planning. This role involves the collection and analysis of data pertaining to website traffic, online campaign advertisements and social media engagement to assess impact and growth. Duties also include responding to all online enquiries across a total of eight social media channels.

## Digital and Social Media Advisor, Case Manager GM Holden/Aegis Australia December 2016 - Present

#### Social Media Management

This has involved monitoring Holden social media channels (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and LiveChat) to identify customer complaints and answer both technical and brand-engagement queries. I became proficient in understanding the importance of brand presence on social media, and developed insight into tracking customer sentiment. In addition, I have established best practice for social interaction and online engagement.

## Case Management

This involved receiving customer issues/complaints and managing such to ensure resolutions were achieved in often challenging circumstances. This skill frequently involved effective communication with both internal and external stakeholders.

### Adhering to KPI's

My affective time management skills and ability to adhere to operational targets was throughly reflected in my work. Examples of such were meeting commitments to our customers, dealers, and internal departments to ensure a high-quality after sales service was delivered at each interaction.

## **Event Supervisor, Fabulous Catering Melbourne February 2014 - Present**

This has involved setting up and running of various functions, including weddings and corporate events. Since beginning in 2014, I have taken on various responsibilities at the company, including waitressing, bar tending and function preparation. These diverse roles including that of an event supervisor, have greatly improved my organisational skills and ability to effectively manage and supervise a team.

## Floor host and Waitress, Little Sparrow Cafe September 2016 - December 2016

Worked as floor host and waitress, this involved food preparation, serving customers and opening/closing of the cafe. The role required the ability to work well in fast-paced environment whilst providing excellent customer service.

## Waitress and Food Counter Attendant, Bouchee Cafe Chadstone October 2015 - September 2016

This work involved opening and closing of the cafe, serving customers, and training new staff. This experience advanced my time management and multi-tasking skills.

#### **Volunteer Experience**

# Writing Assistant, Free to Shine May 2016 - June 2017

Free to Shine is a non-profit organisation which works to prevent sex trafficking and encourage the education of girls in rural Cambodia. By identifying at-risk families in Cambodian villages and providing school equipment and organisational support the NGO aims to ensure the girl's safety and education.

My role involved analysing at-risk girl's application forms and writing/developing information pamphlets to send out to sponsors in Australia, as well as attending

volunteer meetings and assisting with a volunteer fundraising project. This experience gave me insight into the structure and operation of volunteer based organisations, deepening my understanding of how volunteer engagement can be beneficial but requires effective planning and ongoing involvement.

#### **Education**

## RMIT University Melbourne Bachelor of Arts (International Studies) - Completed 2018

My studies at RMIT have established excellent writing and research skills as well as a thorough knowledge of contemporary US politics and governance. Through my completion of Sociology of Drug Use, I became interested in an evidence-based harm reduction approach to drug use and the need for greater drug law reform.

Mount Waverley Secondary College - VCE 2007 - 2012

#### **Skills**

- •Highly Skilled in social media platforms Spredfast and Hootsuite
- Proficient in Customer Relationship Management (CRM) Software (Oracle)
- •Adept at Microsoft Office (Word, Excel and Outlook)

Across my work experiences I have always endeavoured to establish new skills and grow my expertise. In all my various customer service roles, I have advanced and diversified my responsibilities resulting in a strong work ethic and ability to multi-task. My experiences have fostered great professional and personal growth. Moving forward, I feel highly confident and motivated in my ability to furthermore expand my skill set and take the next step in my career development at Drug Policy Alliance.

### References

## **Teneille Nolan**

(Digital Team Leader at GM Holden Customer Care/Aegis Australia) Ph: 0450 373 400